https://www.bootbarn.com/cs-privacy-policy.html

Search
My Store:
Customer Service
If you have any questions or need help with your account, please contact us.
Last updated January, 2020
Boot Barn corporate address: 15345 Barranca Parkway, Irvine, CA 92618
We value the trust you place in BootBarn.com, and we want you to be aware of the safeguards we have in place to respect your privacy. The below policy tells you about the information we gather about you and how we use it. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at custserv@bootbarn.com.
We also do not support SPAM. We are committed to sharing information and advertising promotions to our valued customers and we respect their privacy. Each of our email special promotions come with a simple "unsubscribe link" that permanently removes your address from our list.
This Privacy Policy applies only to this website, our mobile sites, and our use of social media sites (collectively, the “Sites”), and any other personal information obtained when you call, email, or otherwise communicate with BootBarn.com. By accessing the Sites on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other device (collectively, “Device”), making a purchase from BootBarn.com, or otherwise interacting with BootBarn.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the policy, please do not use the Sites.
Types of personal information we may gather
BootBarn.com gathers personal information from you in order to provide superior service, communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you, customize our communications to you, administer our business, and improve your shopping experience. The following are examples of the personal information we gather from you.
Purchases - When you place an order, you give us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address plus payment information. For the information we collect, we are PCI compliant.
Non-Purchases - There may be instances when you are not making a purchase at BootBarn.com and you give us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address, and where applicable, payment information, or when somebody else gives us your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail address, and where applicable, payment information. Some situations when this may occur are when you return or exchange merchandise, receive a gift from BootBarn.com, or enter a contest or participate in a promotion or survey sponsored by Boot Barn, Inc.
Personal Shopping Account - If you create a Personal Shopping Account with us so that you may place orders more conveniently, you authorize us to store your name and shipping address(es).
Catalog Requests - We need your name and address in order to mail you a catalog. We also require a phone number, or e-mail address, so that we can contact you in the unlikely event there is an error in your address, or other delivery problem. To stop receiving catalogs, simply e-mail us at custserv@bootbarn.com.
E-Mail Updates - When you subscribe to receive BootBarn.com e-mail updates featuring exclusive offers (like free shipping), product news, special discounts, contest announcements and more, we require your e-mail address. You can unsubscribe any time by updating your profile here.
We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive about you from other sources, such as address update services. In addition, we may collect personal information from you when you write a review on our Sites. However, we do not ask, and you should not enter, your full name anywhere in your review.
Information We Collect Automatically
When you visit the Sites, we may collect certain information from you, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, MAC address, browser type, operating system, device-identifying information, the specific web pages visited during your connection, and the domain name from which you accessed the Sites. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Sites, the areas or pages of the Sites that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Sites, the number of times you return to the Sites and other clickstream data. We may also use non-personal or aggregated information for statistical analysis, research, and other purposes. We use cookies to help process your order through our website and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access the Sites and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the Sites. To place an order and complete your transaction on BootBarn.com, you must have "cookies" enabled on your Web browser. (If you don't want to enable cookies but would like to place an order, please call us toll free at 1.888.440.2668.) If you have any concerns about leaving cookies on your computer for extended periods, you can delete them using your browser preferences or privacy menus. Note that browser-management tools for cookies are outside of our control and we cannot guarantee their effectiveness.
We may collect other types of personal information such as demographic data (e.g, household income, age, etc.) to our customer records. See below for information about how to request to have your information deleted.
Cookies also help us:
Determine which features and tools you use, and which pages you visit on bootbarn.com
Remember which items you've placed in your shopping bag
Enable you to check out faster if you've created an account with us
We also contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partner, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our site.
We may also use web beacons and/or tracking pixels on the Sites, in our emails, and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your visit to the Sites, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Sites. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors' behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Sites and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information.
We may combine the information we collect through cookies and web beacons with other information we have collected from you or information from other sources.
Use of Information
We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products; (2) to respond to your inquiries; (3) to send you a confirmation email when you make a purchase; (4) to review Site usage and operations; (5) to address problems with the Sites, our business or our services; (6) to protect the security or integrity of the Sites and our business; (7) to monitor the Sites for compliance with our Terms of Use and the law; (8) to contact you with Site updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional materials from us and third party marketing offers from our trusted partners, as well as from other companies; and (9) to provide interest-based advertising to you based on the way you browse and shop on the Sites and other platforms.
Disclosure of Information
We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) to our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties, who may contact you with their own offers; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (5) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about Site users with third parties.
Please note that if you voluntarily submit any personal information for posting on the Sites, such as a review or a blog post, the information becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others, so you should use care before posting information about yourself online.
Our Email Program
If you have agreed to receive marketing emails from us, you can opt out anytime by clicking the unsubscribe link in the emails. We might still send emails to you about your transactions, accounts you have with us and any contests, sweepstakes you have entered. You may still receive marketing text messages if you have opted in to receive them.
Our SMS Program
The mobile operators participating in this campaign are AT&T, Sprint, Virgin Mobile, T-Mobile (T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages), MetroPCS (GSM), U.S. Cellular, and Verizon Wireless. If your mobile operator is not participating, you will not receive a reply to your messages. Some operators may not support some services at the process offered. Pre-paid users may not be able to participate. Check with your mobile operator. Boot Barn collects certain information automatically upon subscription. Information collected includes the type of mobile device you use, unique device identifier and mobile operating system. To opt-in for Boot Barn mobile alerts and offers text BOOTBARN to 20447. By opting in, the Boot Barn mobile subscriber agrees to receive Boot Barn updates and offers via text. You agree to receive recurring mobile marketing text messages from Boot Barn to the mobile number provided by you. Consent is not a condition of purchase. The text messages are generated by an automated dialer from Boot Barn to the provided mobile number. Reply STOP to 20447 cancel. Reply HELP to 20447 for help. Msg & Data Rates May Apply. View Terms.
Children's Privacy at Boot Barn
Boot Barn does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. Boot Barn, Inc is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.
Access, Correction & Deletion
We respect your right to access and correct your personal information. You may access your personal information by signing into your account. From there, you can correct or modify your information. You may also exercise your rights, subject to applicable laws, to request that we delete or restrict access to your personal data. We may need to retain it for legally permitted purposes and this will be explained to you if necessary.
If you need assistance correcting or updating your personal information, or would like to request that we delete your personal information, please contact us using the contact information detailed in the “Contact Us” section below.
Your California Privacy Rights (California Residents)
California residents have the right to request once per calendar year a list of the companies with which we may share personal information for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and a list of the categories of such personal information shared. California residents may make this request by filling out and submitting this web form, by e-mailing privacy@bootbarn.com, or by calling 1-844-901-1870. If emailing, please include "California Privacy Request - Right To Know" in the first line of the description and your California mailing or street address.
If you are a California resident, you also have the right to access, or to request that we delete, any Personal Information we have collected about you, and inquire about our collection, sale and disclosure of your Personal Information. California residents may make this request by filling out and submitting this web form, by e-mailing privacy@bootbarn.com, or by calling us at 1-844-901-1870. If emailing, please include "California Privacy Request - Request to Delete" in the first line of the description and your California mailing or street address.
California residents have the right to opt-out of the sale of their Personal Information where applicable. However, as described in this Privacy Policy, BootBarn.com does not sell Personal Information.
Your exercise of these rights will have no adverse effect on the price and quality of our services.
California residents may request further information about compliance with California law and to make a request under California law by e-mailing privacy@bootbarn.com. Please include "California Privacy Rights Request" in the first line of the description and your California mailing or street address. Please do not include any attachments.
Security
We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner. We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from visitors to the Sites. Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.
Use By Non-US Residents
The Site is operated in the United States under United States law. We do not intentionally offer goods and services to individuals outside of the United States. If you reside in another country, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be collected and stored in the United States or other countries that may have data privacy laws that are less protective than the laws where you reside.
Right to Lodge Complaints
We are transparent about the ways in which we collect and use personal information, and welcome your questions and concerns. If you have any concern or complaint about the way we handle your personal information, please contact us as described below. To the extent you believe we have not addressed your concerns or otherwise choose to do so, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in the country where you reside and/or the United States. You may contact the US Federal Trade Commission regarding your concerns. For more information, please see https://www.ftc.gov/faq/consumer-protection/submit-consumer-complaint-ftc.
Updates
Boot Barn may find it necessary to update this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the revised Policy and the date of the last revision on our website so the consumer is aware of the changes.
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone Number
By submitting this form, I confirm and declare under penalty of perjury that I am the consumer whose personal information is subject to this request.
First Name
Last Name
Email
Phone Number
By submitting this form, I confirm and declare under penalty of perjury that I am the consumer whose personal information is subject to this request.
Thank You. Your request has been received.
An unexpected error occurred processing your request. Please try again later.
